Guide to the Clarence Stein papers, 1905-1983.
Stein, Clarence papers
- Series VIII. Reprints and Articles of Other Professional Planners
  - Klaber, Eugene H.: "Reducing Apartment Costs By Economy" 1932; "In Union There Is Strength" (no date); "What Makes Housing Rental?" 1932; "The Housing Crisis in Paris" (no date); "Report To The Chelsea Planning Committee Of A Preliminary Survey Of The Chelsea District" 1917, 1932, no date (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Klutznick, Phillip M. (Park Forest, Chicago - American Community Builders): "American Community Builders" 1948; "Building A Satellite City" 1947; "Plan of Town in Cook and Will Counties, Illinois" 1947; "Park Forest" plan 1950; Park Forest map and notes, (no date); "Park Forest, Illinois: Proving Ground For Community Planning Techniques" 1951; "Park Forest: A New Design For Better Living" (no date), 1947-1951, no date (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Other O'Harrow, Dennis "Growing Pains of a Village Government", c. 1948 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Kohn, Robert D. "The Government Housing Program", 1934 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Lubove, Roy: "New Cities For Old" 1962; "Lawrence Veiller And The New York State Tenement House Commission of 1900" 1961, 1961-1962 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Community Planning in the 1920's. The Contribution of the Regional Planning Association of America, 1964, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 41A)
    soft cover book, notes
  - The Urban Community Housing and Planning in the Progressive Era, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 41B)
  - MacKaye, Benton: "Employment and Natural Resources" [soft cover book] 1919; "End of Peak of Civilization?" 1932; "Cement Railroads"(no date); "Decentralization" 1951; "Region Building in River Valleys" 1940; "Democracy in Flood Control" 1940; "The Townless Highway" 1930; "Some Early A. T. [Appalachian Trail] History" 1957; "Two Jumps From Lincoln" 1959; "Turns Back Clock" 1959; "Primeval Security" 1948; "Dam Site vs. Norm Site" 1950; "If This Be Snobbery" (no date); "Conservation Units In National Defense: Supplement to "A.R.M." 1941; "A.R.M.: A Primer of National Defense" 1941; "A.R.M.: A Memorandum on Conservation as One of The Three Elements of Nat'l Defense" 1941 [2 copies], 1919-1959, no date (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Geography To Geotechnics: Benton MacKaye Survey 1950-1951: "The Growth of a New Science"; "From Homesteads To Valley Authorities"; "Genesis and Jefferson"; "Folkland as National Maker"; "Washington -- and the Watershed"; "From Continent to Globe"; "Toward Global Law" (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - MacKaye, Benton: "The Montachusett Federalist, Second Series 1950"; "The Montachusett Federalist" (Series One) 1949; "Story Of The Trojan Horse" (no date); "The New Thirteen: Whither State and Region in American Federalism" 1953, 1949-1953, no date (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Also "We Present" Reviews 1947; "Man's Role in Changing The Face of The Earth" review, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - MacKaye, Benton "Benton MacKaye 's Articles on The Four Lives Of A River, etc. 1967", 1966 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - MacKaye, Benton "Regional Planning Adm. Study 1951 Regionalization." 1951-1952, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Mansfeld, Al: "Al Mansfeld" 1965; "Alfred Mansfeld" 1967, 1965, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Mayer, Albert: "Cresting Community -- Part II" 1955; "Public Housing Design" 1963; "Public Housing Architecture" 1962; "New Ways Of Life In Britain's New Towns" 1956; "Let's Plan Our Cities Before It's Too Late 1954; "Greenbelt Towns Re visited" 1968; "New Towns And Defense" 1951; "For A New Way Of City Life" 1946; "Our Cities From Here To Ecumenopolis" 1967; "Attacking The City's Slum Problem: A New Approach" 1934; "Harkins Playful Playground" 1961, 1946-1968 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Mayer, Albert: "Architecture As Total Community: The Challenge Ahead" a series of seven articles; "Crisis And Opportunity" 1964; "Public Housing As Community" 1964; "Urban Renewal As Creative Catalyst" 1964; "Underlying Dynamics Of Social-Physical Development" 1964; "New Towns: And Fresh In-City Communities" 1964; "The Role Of Regional Policy" 1964; "Synthesis And Sublimation: The Role Of The Architect" 1964; "The Metropolitan Region: And Alternatives" 1964; "Climax: Embodiment In Living Architecture" 1964 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Mayer, Albert and Henry Wright and Lewis Mumford "New Homes For A New Deal: A Concrete Program For Slum Clearance and Housing Relief" c. 1934 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Mayer, Arthur L. "Myths and Movies'" 1951 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Merton, Robert K. "Selected Problems Of Field Work In The Planned Community" 1947 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Mumford, Lewis: "The Plan of New York" 1932; "The Plan of New York: II" 1932; "Regional Planning and the Small Town," Parts I and II; "Cities: Forms and Functions" 1968; "Geddes, Patrick" 1968; press release, 1968; clippings, 1967, 1957, 1950, 1961; "Revaluations I: Howard's Garden City" 1965; "The American Way of Death" 1966; "A Regional Plan To Arrest Megalopolis" 1965; "The Future Of The City" a 5-part series, including: "The Disappearing City" 1962, "Yesterday's City of Comorrow" 1962, "Megalopolis As Anti-City" 1962, "Beginning Of Urban Integration" 1963, "Social Complexity And Urban Design" 1963; "Function And Expression In Architecture" 1951; "The Natural History of Urbanization" 1956; "For Older People -- Not Segregation But Integration" 1956 (included in "Buildings For The Aged" Architectural Record, 1956; "The City As Both Heaven And Hell: a conversation between Graeme Shankland and Lewis Mumford" 1961 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Mumford, Lewis: "The Human Prospect And Architecture" 1959; "The Highway and the City" 1958; "A New Approach to Workers' Housing" 1957; "The Human Way Out" 1961; "First Annual Purvis Memorial Lecture: The New World Promise" 1965; "A Thought For a Growing South" 1949; "Planning For The Phases Of Life" 1949; "The Social Foundations Of Post-War Building" 1943; "The Plan Of London County" 1945; "The Culture Of Cities, A Review" 1938; "Atom Bond: Miracle or Catastrophe" 1948; "Social Effects" 1947; "The Morals Of Extermination" (no date); "Break The Housing Blockage" 1933; "Mass Production And The Modern House" Parts I and II, 1936; "Regionalism And Irregionalism: The Regional Outlook" 1927; "The Theory And Practice Of Regionalism: From Palotechnic To Neotechnic" 1928; "The Theory And Practice Of Regionalism: The Superiorities Of A Regional City" 1928; "Cities Old And New" Parts I, II, III, 1926 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Lewis Mumford: Skyline: New Yorker: "Mother Jacob's Home Remedies" 12-1-62; "London and the Laocoon" 11-4-61; "Unesco House I" 11-12-60; "Unesco House II" 11-19-60; "The Skyway's The Limit" 11-14-59; "The Red-Brick Beehives" 5-16-50; "The Roaring Traffic's Boom -- I" 3-18-55; "The Roaring Traffic's Boom -- II" 4-2-55; "The Roaring Traffic's Boom -- III" 4-16-55; "The Roaring Traffic's Boom -- IV" 6-11-55; "More Pelion, More Ossa" 2-3-51; "Babel In Europe" 9-28-57; "The Marseilles 'Folly'" 10-5-57; "The Lesson of the Master" 9-13-58; "Crystal Lantern" 11-13-54; also: "Books: Where The Great City Spreads 3-3-56; and a review by Brendan Gill: "Books: Homage to Mr. Mumford" 8-12-61 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Pomeroy, Hugh R. (Director, Westchester County Dept. of Planning): "Dispersion By Reason Or By Ruin" 1948; "Putting our Plan to Work" 1949; Statement on planning aspects of provision of proposed housing legislation relating to urban development -- before Senate Committee on Banking and Currency, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Rasmussen, Steen Eiler "Neighborhood Planning" 1957 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Regional Plan Association Bulletin #96 "Race For Open Space" Final Report of Park, Recreation and Open Space Project. 1960; Bulletin #99 "Hub Bound Travel" 1961 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Smith, G.E. Kidder "How To Photograph Architecture" 1959 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Stephenson, Gordon: "The Physical Planning Of Universities" 1965; "Planning For Reconstruction" (no date) (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Stone, Edward D. "Brussels Pavilion" 1957 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Town Planning Review "Islamabad, The Creation of a New Capital" Doxiadis, C.A. 1965 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Tyrwhitt, Jacqueline "The Size and Spacing of Urban Communities" 1949 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Unwin, Raymond "The Architect and His City" 1926 (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Vance, John E. "Planning The Metropolitan District" c. 1947 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Von Eckcirdt, Wolf "Greenbelt -- A Town's Fading Dream" 1967 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Walker, Ralph: "The Architect As a Student" 1949; "Land Use" "Books -- Design and Contents" (no date); "Centennial Medal of Honor," an award from A.I.A., 1957; "[Architectural Character of Capital Buildings]" 1962 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - Wank, Roland A. (head architect, TVA), Work of Friend Wank, T.V.A. Community Buildings: Pictures: "TVA" 1939; "Architecture in Rural Areas" 1942; "Rural Activities Center, Tenn. Valley" 1944; "Planned Communities" 1943 (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Willcox, Roger "Cooperative Techniques and Effective Reduction in Housing Costs" 1953 (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - Wood, Edith Elmer "Slums and Blighted Areas in the United States" 1935 (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - Woodard, Chloethiel Smith "From Rant to Space" 1936 (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - Wright, Henry: "To Plan or Not To Plan" 1932; "Notes and Comments: Application of Apartment House Data To An Actual Layout" a criticism of H.W., (no date); "How Can Apartment Facilities Be Provided For The Low-Income Groups?" 1932; Servicing Apartments For Lower Rentals" 1933; "The Autobiography of Another Idea" 1930; "What Does The Architect Know About Small House Costs?" 1931; "Hillside Group Housing" 1932; "The Architect And Small House Costs" 1932 (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - Wurster, William W.: "Row House Vernacular and High Style Monument" 1958; "Sunset Community Center, San Francisco: Forty-Three Acres Cooperatively Planned 1952; Other: Wurster & Bauer: "Indian Vernacular Architecture: Wai and Cochin", (no date); "Tributes For Catherine B. Wurster" (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - No Author: "Spatial Variety in Two Museums" 1965; "One Good Civic Center Doesn't Make A City" 1966 (Box 18, Folder 74)
- Series IX. Sketches, Drawings, Plans and Maps
  - Stevenage drawing, planned English town, Plot Plan or property in Westchester Co.(CSS's vacation home) [copies] 1950's c_.1935 (Box 19)
  - Sketchbook of architectural drawings (Box 41)
  - Pencil sketch at Modena, facade cathedral Jan. 5, 1915 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Pencil sketch, plan and elevation Feb. 27, 1915 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Pencil sketch Feb. 20, 1915 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Pencil sketch, baptistry of cathedral 1915 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Pencil sketch, metalwork/Mexican Dec. 1914 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Invitation line drawing 1916 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Duplicate 41-6 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Pencil sketches, cartoons French Provincials in Florence June 6, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Notes and sketches Venice (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Notes and sketches Italy July 1950 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Notes and sketches Museums, Paris, Rotterdam 1950 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Notes and sketches Nancy 1950 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Notes and sketches Florence July 1950 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Notes and sketches Versailles, Chartres 1950 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Notes and sketches Piazza Sa. Pietro July 1950 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Pencil sketch Venice (deteriorated condition) and photographic copy Sept. 1909 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Pencil sketch Versailles c. 1906-1911 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Watercolor sketch [fortress] c. 1906-1911 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Watercolor sketch exterior c. 1906-1911 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Watercolor wash (urban architecture) c. 1906-1911 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Pencil studies Versailles, details c. 1906-1911 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Watercolor study, decorative motif c. 1906-1911 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Conte drawing, carving on tomb c. 1906-1911 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Pencil studies decorative details Versailles c. 1906-1911 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Watercolor, doorway exterior view c. 1906-1911 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Pencil study National Museum, Florence c. 1906-1911 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Watercolor studies fragments de ceramique c. 1906-1911 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Watercolor study frieze and moldings c. 1906-1911 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Watercolor study surface designs c. 1906-1911 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Watercolor study Europe c. 1906-1911 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Watercolor study interior of church c. 1906-1911 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Photograph clay model c. 1906-1911 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Watercolor statue Mercury c. 1906-1911 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Watercolor study religious c. 1906-1911 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Watercolor study garden and pool c. 1906-1911 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - 4 watercolor studies decorative detail Chateau Blois Aug. 1906 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Pencil and watercolor Chateau Blois Aug. 6, 1906 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - Pencil sketch Loches Aug. 18, 1906 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Conte drawing San Zeno, Verona April 6, 1907 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Charcoal and chalk drawing candelabra base May 8, 1907 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Pencil sketch architectural detail c. 1907 (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - 4 charcoal sketches (multiple) Along the Rhine c. 1907 (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Pencil and chalk sketch Ospe dal Maggiore, Milan April 2, 1907 (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - Pencil sketch Blois Sept. 7, 1907 (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - Pencil sketch Trocadero, details Sept. 12, 1907 (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - Pencil sketch sculpture and decoration S. Kensington Museum Sept. 7/8, 1908 (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - Watercolor study to scale, decoration Rome June 4, 1909 (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - Watercolor study of tomb decoration Florence July 14, 1909 (Box 41, Folder 47)
  - Watercolor study, Florence July 15, 1909 (Box 41, Folder 48)
  - Pencil sketches, choir stall San Pietro Perugia July 3, 1909 (Box 41, Folder 49)
  - 2 sections of watercolor sketches Florence Aug. 1909 (Box 41, Folder 50)
  - 2 pencil/wash studies tombs, Florence July 10, 1909 (Box 41, Folder 51)
  - Watercolor sketch, courtyard with fountain, Bologne Aug. 1909 (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - Watercolor sketch arches (Italy) 1909 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - 1 watercolor sketch, tower 1 colored pencil sketch, tower c. 1906-1911 c. 1906-1911 (Box 41, Folder 53)
  - 1 pencil sketch, cathedral, Avila May 5, 1910 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - 1 pencil sketch, detail of courtyard corner April 30, 1910 (Box 41, Folder 54)
  - 1 pencil sketch (unfinished) courtyard Casa del Greco, Toledo April 30, 1910 (Box 41, Folder 55)
  - Watercolor sketch, Rome 1911 (Box 41, Folder 56)
  - Watercolor sketch, Pisa Aug. 4, 1911 (Box 41, Folder 57)
  - 2 watercolors on Bristol Board [San Diego] c. 1915 (Box 41, Folder 58)
  - 2 ink cartoons of C. S. Stein c. 1915-1920 (Box 41, Folder 59)
  - Photograph [lake and woodland shore] undated (Box 41, Folder 60)
  - Chalk, charcoal, conte sketch winter scene, NYC apartment Feb. 15, 1955 (Box 41, Folder 61)
  - Pastel NYC view To My Valentine c. 1955 (Box 41, Folder 62)
  - Pastel sketch (preparatory) view from NYC c. 1955 (Box 41, Folder 63)
  - Sevenage (negative print of sketch) 1951 (Box 41, Folder 64)
  - Wichita Museum details: architectural plans (copies) Nov. 1929 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Wichita Museum details: architectural plans (copies) Nov. 1929 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Wichita Museum details: architectural plans (copies) Nov. 1929 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - (Box 41, Folder 65)
  - Pencil sketch Bologne c. 1906-1911 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - 2 pencil sketches Chartres Aug. 23, 1906 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - 2 pencil sketches Verona April 1907 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Charcoal studies Nurnberg July 1907 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Pencil sketch Chester (half timber facade) Aug. 14, 1908 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Pencil sketch Chartres Oct. 6, 1908 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Watercolor sketch, Florence, July 17, 1909 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Pencil sketch, Florence July 22, 1909, July 22, 190 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - 2 pencil sketches, Casa del Credo, April 30, 1910 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Pencil sketch, Rouen undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Pencil sketch, Lincoln Cathedral, August 22, 1908 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Watercolor, Ronda, 1910 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Clarence Stein and family, 1878-1900 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Europe, family, friends, Clarence Stein, 1905-1911 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - 2 photographs: Clarence Stein at Goodhue's office, Mumford and MacKaye, c. 1912 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Stein Family, 50th wedding anniversary of Leo and Rose, 1928 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Clarence Stein with family and friends, California, 1930-1940 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Clarence Stein and A. M.S. trip to Orient(4 months), 1936-1937 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Clarence Stein family and friends(N.Y. and New England), 1930-1939 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Travel photographs 19^0-1955 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - 1 photo Greendale, Wisconsin, anniversary, 1948 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Benton MacKaye, photo, drawings (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Clarence Stein, family and friends, N.Y. area, 1940-1955 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Photograph of Clarence Stein, E. Bacon, S.. Rassmussen, Philadelphia, 1950s (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - 1 photograph, Color: Clarence Stein and A. M.S., "La Casa", 1942 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Clarence Stein and friends, 1955-1970 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Clarence Stein with Planning Students at Radburn, 1960 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Clarence Stein and A. M.S., on their N.Y.C. balcony, c. 1960 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Clarence Stein and friend, c. 1960-1970 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Clarence Stein at home, last 6 years of his life, 1960s-1970s (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - photographs of 'Thousand Years' vacation home (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Views from Stein's N.Y.C. apartment (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Portraits of Clarence Stein (8) (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Sketches of Clarence Stein by A. M.S. (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Invitations drawn by Clarence Stein (Box 43, Folder 23)
- Series X. Diaries, Journals, Albums, bills, passport, W. W. I. records 1897-1972 (Box 27)
- Series XI. Published Material, Books (Box 25)
- Series XII. Certificates, pamphlets, projects and postcards
  - Certificates, pamphlets, projects and postcards (Box 26)
  - Minutes and records of Regional Development Council of American and 'The Snag Club', 1949-1953 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Published material on community development (pamphlets and articles), 1951-1976 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Christmas card, hand-printed "To Clarence" (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Publications & sketches concerning social events at B. G. Goodhue's office (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Defense Housing Project Stowe & Shaler Twp. Working Drawings & Plans, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - El Dorado Hills New Town Victor Gruen - Planner Brochure; near Sacramento, California, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Crestwood Estates Residential Development Royal Ridge Near Perth, Australia References to Radburn (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Plan D'amenagement et D'organisation generale de la region Parisienne- Paris Regional Plan, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Architect's License State of Pennsylvania, June 17, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Architect's License State of New York Replacing original issued December 1, 1916, July 17, 1935 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Architect's License State of New Jersey, July 10, 1919 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Kitimat British Columbia Townsite Report, 1952-1955 & 1958 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Series XIII. Oversized items
  - Spuyten Duyvil Housing, Bronx, NY; Quantity-9, 1923 (Folder 1)
  - Sunnyside Gardens, Long Island City, N.Y.; Quantity - 6, 1924-1925 (Folder 2)
  - Sunnyside, Long Island City, N.Y., 9 photographs, 2 plans, 1924; Formerly Box 38 Folder 16 (Folder 2a)
  - Sunnyside, Long Island City, N.Y., 11 photographs, 1924; Formerly Box 38 Folder 17 (Folder 2b)
  - California Institute of Technology Pasadena, CA; Quantity - 6, 1927 (Folder 3)
  - "Museum of To-morrow" Museum in Theory /unpublished book; Quantity - 15 (Folder 4)
  - [City Development Plan] [Los Angeles], Cal.; Quantity - 7; undetermined (Folder 5)
  - Radburn, N.J.; Quantity - 1, August 1, 1930 (Folder 6)
  - Greenbelt, Md.; Quantity - 1, 1953 (Folder 7)
  - Baldwin Hills, Los Angeles, Cal.; Quantity - 3, 1939 (Folder 8)
  - Ramat-Aviv Neighborhood Unit No. 1 Tel-Aviv, Israel; Quantity - 1, 1959 (Folder 9)
  - Radburn Type Plan by Markelius near [Stockholm] Sweden; Quantity - 6, 1946-1951 (Folder 10)
  - Museum of Modern Art N.Y., N.Y.; Quantity - 43, February 1938-February 1939 (Folder 11)
  - Costume Institute N.Y.C. Metropolitan Museum of Art; Quantity - 7, 1956; Map case Folder 12 (Folder 12)
  - Columbus Circle N.Y., N.Y.; Quantity - 4, 1949 (Folder 13)
  - Proposed Princeton Museum Princeton, N. J.; Quantity - 37, 1931, undated (Folder 14)
  - Proposed Princeton Museum Princeton, N.J.; Quantity - 46, 1932 (Folder 15)
  - Proposed Princeton Museum Princeton, N.J.; Quantity - 9, 1933 (Folder 16)
  - Proposed Princeton Museum Princeton University Princeton, N.J.; Quantity - 5, 1934 (Folder 17)
  - Proposed Princeton Museum; Quantity - 53; 1935, 1935 (Folder 18)
  - Radburn Plans, Ink on Linen; Quantity - 5, 1931 (Folder 19)
  - Hillside Gardens, 1934 (Folder 20)
  - Plans for Comm. 223 Main House 1000 years, 1939 (Folder 21)
  - Awards/certificates; misc. cartoons; photo of Ecole Nationale des Beaux Arts, Atelier Laloux 1910; misc. maps (Folder 22)
  - Radburn Plan, Ink on Linen; Quantity - 1, 1931 (Folder 23)
- Series XIV. Phonographs and Other Media
  - 2 aluminum phonographs titled "WEVD 8:15", 1939; SR-1226-1227 (Box 38)
  - "Dispersal of Cities", Paul Greer, 1951; SR-1228 (Box 38)
  - Baldwin Hills Village: 'A Village in a City,' " 1942-1950, V-1453 (Box 52)
    Videotape by Reginald D. Johnson, copied from the 16mm color original film.